Guide to the Patricia England fine print collection, 1970s-1980s
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Patricia England fine print collection
1970s-1980s
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Patricia G. England
C0076
5 linear ft.; 13 boxes
This collection contains numerous journals, catalogs, pamphlets, and newsletters on "fine print" (private press) books. Materials include around twenty issues each of the journals "The Book Collector," "Devil's Artisan," "Konglomerati," and nearly forty issues of "The Private Library" as well as promotional pamphlets and ephemera from numerous fine printing presses including Acorn, Arion, Book Club of California, Pennyroyal, and Somesuch Press.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Patricia England in 1993.
Biographical Information
Patricia G. England is a collector of "fine print" (private press) books.
Scope and Content
This collection contains numerous journals, catalogs, pamphlets, and newsletters on "fine print" (private press) books and material pertaining to the history of book collecting, publishing and printing, including information and/or samples from a number of presses and publishing companies. Materials include around twenty issues each of the journals "The Book Collector," "Devil's Artisan," "Konglomerati," and nearly forty issues of "The Private Library" as well as promotional pamphlets and ephemera from numerous fine printing presses including Acorn, Arion, Book Club of California, Pennyroyal, and Somesuch Press.
Series 1 contains periodicals on book collecting as well as printing practices and history.
Series 2 and 3 contain information and sample materials from a number of printing presses, sorted alphabetically.
Series 4 contains pamphlets and exhibition material from a variety of eras and places.
Series 5 contains broadsides, keepsakes and advertisements from a number of companies and artists. The material in this series is oversized and resides separately from the boxed portion of the collection.
Arrangement
Organized into five series.
Series 1: Periodicals, 1980-1992 (Boxes 1-8)
Series 2: Ephemera A-C, 1975-1992 (Boxes 8-9)
Series 3: Ephemera D-Z, 1969-1997 (Boxes 9-11)
Series 4: Pamphlets, Miscellaneous, 1962-1990 (Boxes 11-12)
Series 5: Oversize 1979-1989 (Box 13)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives holds several thousand volumes of.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Fine books.; Private press books.; Rare books.
Contents List
- Series 1: Periodicals, 1980-1992; (7.5 boxes)
  This series contains a number of periodicals and newsletters with information on book collecting and printing history.
  - American Book Collector, Vols. 1-6, Nos. 1-6, January/February 1980 - November/December 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
  - American Book Collector, Vol. 7, Nos. 1-8, 10-12, January 1986 - December 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - American Book Collector, Vol., Nos. 1-6, January 1987 - June 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - American Printing History Association, The Alpha Letter, Nos. 19-45, 47-67, 81-82, 94, 1979-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Book Collector's Market, Vol. 2, Nos. 1-6; Vol. 4, Nos. 1-6, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Book Club of California Quarterly Newsletter, 17 issues, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Vol. 43, Nos. 3-4; Vol. 44, Nos. 1-4; Vol. 45, Nos. 1-2. 4; Vol. 46, Nos. 1-4; Vol. 47, Nos. 1, 3-4; Vol. 48, No. 1
  - The Book Club of California Quarterly Newsletter, 16 issues, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Vols. 31-40; Vol. 48, Nos. 2-4; Vol. 49, Nos. 1-4; Vol. 50, Nos. 1-4; Vol. 51, Nos. 1-4
  - The Book Club of California Quarterly Newsletter, 18 issues, 1986-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Vol. 52, Nos. 1, 3-4; Vol. 53, Nos. 2-4; Vol. 54, Nos. 1-4; Vol. 55, Nos. 1; Vol. 56, nos. 3-4; Vol. 57, Nos. 1-3; Vol. 58, Nos, 1-2
  - The Book Collector, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Vol. 31, No. 4; Vol. 32, Nos. 1-3
  - The Book Collector, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Vol. 32, No. 4; Vol. 33, Nos. 1-3
  - The Book Collector, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Vol. 33, No. 4; Vol. 34, Nos. 1-3 (Vol. 34, No. 1, misnumbered as Vol. 32, No. 1)
  - The Book Collector, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Vol. 34, No. 4; Vol. 35, Nos. 1-3
  - The Book Collector and The Devil's Artisan, 1986-1987; 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Vol. 35, No. 4; Vol. 36, No. 1-2; The Devil's Artisan, Nos. 5-7
  - The Devil's Artisan, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Nos. 8-18
  - The Devil's Artisan, 1986-1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Nos. 19-27
  - Guild of Book Workers Journal, Vol. 20, Nos. 1-2, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Konglomerati (periodical), Vol. 6, Nos. 1-4, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Printing History, Vol. 1-7, Nos. 1-2, 1979-1985 (Box 5)
  - Printing History, Vols. 8-13, Nos. 1-2; Vol. 14, No. 1, 1986-1992 (Box 6)
  - The Private Library, 1970; 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Second Series, Vol. 3, Nos. 3-4; Third Series, Vol. 3, Nos. 1-4; Vol. 3, Nos. 1-3
  - The Private Library, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Third Series, Vol. 4, No. 4; Vols. 5-6, Nos. 1-4
  - The Private Library, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Third Series, Vols. 7-10
  - The Private Library, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Fourth Series, Vols. 1-3
  - Private Libraries Association, 1980-1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Newsletters, Nos. 92-93, 96, 99, 107, 118; Exchange Lists, Nos 92-93, 99, 118; Organization Description; Meeting Agenda
  - Small Press, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Vol. 1, No. 6; Vol 2, Nos. 1-3
  - Typographic, 1975-1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Vol. 7, Nos. 2-3; Vol 8, No. 1; Vol. 14, Nos. 2, 4; Vol. 15, No. 2
  - Bancroftiana, No. 92, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Boldeian Library Record, Vol. 10, No. 6, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Imprint of the Stanford Libraries Association, Vol. 9, No. 1, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - John and Mary's Journal, No. 8, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Record, No. 12, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Versal, January, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Series 2: Ephemera A-C, 1975-1992; (1 box)
  This series contains material related to a number of printing presses, including Christmas cards, business cards, brochures, prospectuses, and publication announcements.
  - Acorn Press, 1975; 1984; 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Christmas Cards, Invitation to No-Name Book Group
  - Adastra Press, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Pamphlet (poetry titles), 2 Publication Announcements (Through the Mother Ditch, Sea Fire)
  - Allen Press, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    3 Publication Announcements (Romeo and Juliet, 1988; The Poeticon Atronomicon, 1985; Egypt: Herodotus: Fifth Century B. C., 1989)
  - American Antiquarian Society, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Seminar Announcement
  - Anachronic Editions (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Publication Announcement (Collotype)
  - Ann Muir Marbling (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Brochure with paper samples
  - Anvil Press, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Correspondence (notecard), Publication Announcement (Poems by Li Po, 1984)
  - Arif Press, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Invitation, Note on Publication Delays (Ars Poetica, 1989)
  - Arion Press, 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Christmas Cards (1983, 1985-1987, 1989), Keepsake (A Wartime Letter from Jane Grabhorn to S/Sgt. Albert Sperisen... 1980), 6 Publication Announcements (le Desert De Retz, 1990; Wallace Stevens Poems, 1985; The Maltese Falcon, 1983; Flatland; The Lay of the Love and Death of Cornet Cristoph Rilke, 1983; Tristam Shandy, 1988; United States Constitution, 1987
  - Arion Press, 1982; 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Pamphlet, 2 Publication Announcements (The Typefoundry in Silhouette; The Book of Common Prayer, 1982)
  - Ashling Press, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Publication Announcement (The Art of Papermaking, 1976)
  - Associates of the University of California Press, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Description, Invitation
  - Barbarian Press, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Publication Announcement (Sorts and Founts, 1983)
  - Bieler Press, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Christmas Card, Catalog (984), 5 Publication Announcements (The 24 Doors, 1985; moon, 1983; A Printer's Dozen; Five Small Meditations on Summer and Birds, 1984; The Compleat Melancholick, 1985)
  - Bird and Bull Press, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Announcement and Postcard concerning Artsman Organization and Tiller, Publication Announcement (Tiller, Vol. 2, 1984)
  - Book Arts press, 1983-1984, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Christmas Cards
  - Book Club of California - Postcards (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Invitations
  - Book Club of California - Announcements and Prospectuses, 1979-1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Announcements, Invitations, Memorial for Sherwood Grover, 2 Series of Keepsake Folders (Lithographic Views of California Towns, 1875-1889, 1-10, 1985; Chinese Book Arts and California, 1-12, 1989), 9 Public Announcements (Dan De Quille of the Big Bonanza, 1980; A Trumpet of Our Own, 1981; A Western Journey with Mr. Emerson, 1979; Romualdo Pacheco..., 1985; At the Sign of the lark, 1983; Frank Morrison Pixley..., 1989; Letters to Elizabeth, 1977; Paul Landacre, 1982' The Rhemes New Testament, 1990)
  - Book Club of California - Announcements and Prospectuses, 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Memorial for Lawton Kennedy, Keepsake (California Printing, Part Two, 1981), 16 Public Announcements (The Log of Apollow, 1986; Art Deco, 1987; Thomas Bewick and the Fables of Aesop, 1983; California Wine-making, 1978; The Grabhorn Press, 1981-82; A Matter of Taste, 1979; Isadora Duncan and Gordon Craig, 1988; Texas Argonauts, 1987; Mexico on Stone, 1984; Edward Vischer's Drawings..., 1982; Themes in Aquatint. 1978; Redwood and Lumbering..., 1983; From Kapuvar to California, 1979; A Book on Gaelic Arts..., 1989; Frank Norris: Collected Letters, 1986; An Artist records the California Missions, 1989)
  - Book Club of California - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Invitations, Membership Notifications, Memorial for Joseph M. Bransten
  - Book club of Texas (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Announcements, Invitations
  - Boxwood Press (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Publication Announcement (The Song of Songs, with 4 postcards)
  - Bridwell Library, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Publication Announcement (Anglican Liturgy... - Catalog, 1985)
  - Bromer Booksellers, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Christmas Cards (1982-1983), 2 Public Announcements (The Cask of Amontillado, 1981; Shall I Die? Shall I Fly?)
  - Buttonmaker Press (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Empty
  - Cambridge University Library (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Catalog Sheet
  - Catawba Press, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Christmas Cards for Smith College Library, 2 Publication Announcements (Shaker Herbs, 1984; Of the Small Silver-couloured Book-worm)
  - Century Editions, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Publication Announcement (The Sphinx, 1981)
  - Chama Press (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Publication Announcement (Artistry in Single Action)
  - Chelondiidae Press, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Christmas Cards (1985-1986), Series List, 2 Publication Announcements (The Jumping Frog, 1985; The Black Cat, 1984)
  - Chiswick Book Shop, 1982, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Christmas Pamphlet (1982), Invitation, Publication Announcement (The Book of Joseph, 1991)
  - Coffee House Press, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Catalog associated with Toothpaste Press
  - Corycian Press, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Catalogs
  - Cummington Press (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Publication Announcement (Northern Interior)
- Series 3: Ephemera D-Z, 1969-1997; (2 boxes)
  - David R. Godine, Publisher (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Newsletters, Selected Books in Print Catalogues, 2 Publication Announcements (Rails of the World, Specimen Days)
  - Dawson's Bookshop, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Publication Announcement (Paul Landacre, 1983)
  - DeGolyer Library, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Publication Announcement (Book Stalking.../ Return to the Heartland, 1987)
  - Doltroon Press (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Publication Announcement (Halos of Debris)
  - Earl and Ivan Kallemeyn, Printers, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Keepsake (Psalm XXII)
  - Ecco Press, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Publication Announcement (Dante's Inferno, 1993)
  - Edition Seefeld (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Publication Announcement (Tagebuch Der Reise...)
  - Emanon Press, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Publication Announcement (Las Piedras del Cielo, 1981)
  - Ex Ophidia Books, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Books in Print Folder
  - Five Trees Press (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Invitation
  - French Publishing Corporation, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Publication Announcement (Plain John Wiltshire..., 1989)
  - Friends of the Bancroft Library (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Friends of the Shakespeare Press Museum (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Publication Announcement(The Penetrating Light...)
  - Friends of Smith College Library (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Fritz and Trudi Eberhardt (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Business Card/ Folder
  - Gehenna Press, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Exhibition Checklist
  - Gemelli Press, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Publication Announcement (A Sound Beyond, 1989)
  - Gleeson Library Associates, 1969-1991 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Christmas Cards (1969, 1978, 1983, 1984, 1986, 1989, 1990, 1991)
  - Granary Books (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Publication Announcement (Firebird)
  - Greenwood Press, 1979-1993 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Advertisement for Program at Center for Typographic Language, List of Books (1992-1993 Publication), 3 Publication Announcements (Book One by Horace, 1981; A Search for the Typographic Form of Plato's Phaedrus, 1979)
  - Grenfell Press, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Catalog
  - Grolier Club, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Heyeck Press, 1982-1993 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Christmas Cards (1982, 1984, 1993), Card Relating to 1989 Earthquake, Publication Announcement (Sources)
  - Hiersoux, Powers, Thomas, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    Publication Announcement (Mulberry Women, 1982)
  - Hollow Press (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Publication Announcement (Uncle E's Lessons...)
  - Iguana Press, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Christmas Cards (1981, 1982, 1984), Titles in Print, Address Slip, Birth Announcement
  - Interval Press (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Booklist
  - Irish Pig Press (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - James, the Printer, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    Publication Announcement (The Elston Press..., 1997)
  - Jeffrey Thomas, Fine and Rare Books, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Jester Press, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    Publication Announcement (Linocuts of edward B. Heffernan, 1982)
  - Jo Ann Reister, Ltd., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    Publication Announcement (Alphabetarium, 1982)
  - John Howell - Books (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Business Cards
  - Jordan Davies, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Poetry Catalog, Publication Announcement (Father Abraham, 1983)
  - Kairo Press (Box 10, Folder 3)
    2 Publication Announcements (Just Such a Time; The Stone Beloved)
  - Kathleen Gray Schallock (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Artwork Offer
  - Keynes Press, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - King Library Press (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Publication Announcement (Arcades)
  - Peter Kock, Printer, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Christmas Cards for Steven Corey (1989), Business Cards, Invitation for Nob Hill Association (1982)
  - Konglomerati Press, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Catalog, 2 Publication Announcements (Florida Poems, Catnip Pie)
  - Kutanai Press (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Lab Press (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Christmas Card
  - Labyrinth Editions, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Larkspur Press (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Catalogue
  - Leopard's Head Press, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Publication Announcement (The Moon Dies, 1982)
  - Libanus Press, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Library of Congress, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Brochure
  - Library Fellows of Whitney Museum of American Art (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Publication Announcement (The View)
  - James Linden, Publisher, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, 2 Publication Announcements (The Fates of Rocks and Trees; Apology for Bad Dreams, 1986)
  - Limited Editions Club, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Chrismas Cards, Series Catalogs, Newsletters
  - M Kimberly Press (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Publication Announcement (Purifying the Language of the Tribe)
  - Matrix Press, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, Five Trees Press Ephemera Catalog, 3 Publication Announcements (Chimera Broadsides series, The Indians in the Woods, Red Light with Blue Sky)
  - Meadow Press, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Catalog, 5 Publication Announcements (Small Hymns; Shaving at Night, 1982; Cracked Open; Leon; Black Waters)
  - Mink Brook Editions, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Publication Announcement (Poster by Lance Hidy, 1988)
  - MIT Press (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Publication Announcement (Thomas Bewick)
  - Moving Parts Press, 1985-1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Catalog, Correspondence, 3 Publication Announcements (The Rain, 1985; Fair Entry, 1990; The Hand Correspondence, 1990)
  - Mt. Tam Press, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Keepsake Printed for Roxburghe Club
  - No-Name Rare Book Group (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Nova Cards (Box 10, Folder 27)
    Card
  - Occasional Works, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Publications Announcement (Still Life and Other Poems, 1987)
  - Pacific Center for the Book Arts/ Friends of the San Francisco Library, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Parallel Editions (Box 10, Folder 30)
    Project Catalog
  - Penmaen Press, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    Books in Print List, Catalogs, Newsletter, Advertisement for Notecards, Publication Announcement (Face to Face - series of engravings)
  - Pennyroyal Press, 1976-1987 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Catalogs (1976, 1980), 2 Advertisements for Moser Engraving Pieces, 5 Publication Announcements (Frankenstein, 1984; The Robber Bridegroom, 1987; Man in a Metal Cage, 1977; Eve, Singing, 1976; Above the Oxbow [reads "Catawba Press])
  - Penstemon Press, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, Lithograph Reproductions, Catalogs, Artist Resume, Publication Announcement (Aubade, 1980)
  - Penumbra Press, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    Valentine Card, Books in Print List, 2 Publication Announcements (Good Evening and Other Poems, Keeping the Night)
  - Pittsburgh Bibliographies, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    Invitation (1981), Memorial for Agnes Lynch Starrett (1988)
  - Plain Wrapper Press (Box 10, Folder 36)
    Correspondence, Article, Description, Publication Announcement (Will and Testament)
  - Plough Press, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    Publication Announcement (Patterns and Pigments in English Marbled Papers, 1988)
  - Prairie Press (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Press at Colorado College (Box 10, Folder 39)
    Publication Announcement (Tattoo Parlor...)
  - Press in Tuscany Alley (Box 10, Folder 40)
    Wine Label, Publication Announcement (The Swing)
  - Press of the Golden Key (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Press of Appletree Alley (Box 10, Folder 42)
    2 Publication Announcements (Adam and Eve, The Man Who Loved Islands)
  - Press of the Palace of Governors, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    2 Publication Announcements (My New Mexico Literary Friends; Broncho vs. Bicycle, 1987)
  - Private Press, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Protean Press (Box 10, Folder 45)
    Publication Announcement (Maya)
  - Pyracantha Press, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    Publication Announcement (The Warrington Poems, 1989)
  - Rainbow Press (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Rampant Lions Press (Box 10, Folder 48)
    Publication Announcement (Root and Sky)
  - Reading Lion Press, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Red Gull Press, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    Correspondence, Publication Announcement (Majnun Laila, 1985)
  - Red Ozier Press, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    Correspondence, Postcard (1984), Publication Lists (1982, 1983, 1984), Christmas Cards, 4 Publication Announcements (Father Abraham, 1983; Careless Love, 1985; One Day of Happiness, 1982; Looking for Beethoven in Las Vegas, 1983)
  - Rocket Press, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    Catalog, Publication Announcement (Alice in Wonderland - Series of Engravings [references Macmillan Publishers Ltd.])
  - Roger Beachum, Publisher (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Publication Announcement (Old Maid's Folly, Black Venus, and Other Texas legal Tales)
  - Rosemary Press (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Sacramento Book Collectors Club, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Publication Announcement (John A. Sultev's Last Days, 1986)
  - St. Paul's Bibliographies, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Sandstone Press, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Scarab Press, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Publication Announcement (Printing Poetry, 1980)
  - Scolar Press (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Bookmark Advertisement for Latin Edition of Wizard of Oz, Publication Announcement (Three Stories of the Raj)
  - Sea Pen Press and Paper Mill (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Notes, Publication Announcement (Even Money)
  - Shelly Hoyt (Formerly Black Stone Press) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Invitation, Business Card, Publication List, 2 Publication Announcements (Reflections on Color, The Circus of Most Inventions)
  - Silver Buckle Press (Box 11, Folder 10)
    3 Publication Announcements (Calendar of Ornamental Material; The Significance of the Frontier; O'Ryan's Belt)
  - Somesuch Press, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Series Announcement (1978), Name Card, 7 Publication Announcements (Little Manvel; The Wars of the Words, 1980; Portraits of the Queen, 1979; Certain Unalienable Rights, 1982; Love, 1983; Christmas Stamps, 1982; Pueblo Art, 1983)
  - Stone House Press, 1978-1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Swamp Press (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Correspondence
  - Taurus Books, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Tern Press (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Business Description, Forthcoming Titles Card, Folder
  - Theodore Press (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Publication Announcement (A Winter Walk)
  - Tidal Press, 1977-1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, Books for Sale Lists (1979), Prospectus for 1977-1985
  - Toothpaste Press, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Books in Print List (1982), New Titles Flyer (1980), Catalogs (1981, 1983), Publication Announcement (A Visit from St. Alphabet)
  - Turkey Press (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Stolen and Contaminated Poems
  - Twowindows Press (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, Catalog, 3 Publication Announcements (Devour the Fire; Bromeliaceae Andreanae; With a Heart Full of Love)
  - Unidentified (Box 11, Folder 21)
    2 Publication Announcements (Guillem de Poitou; The Hour of the Bell)
  - University of California Press, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    Publication Announcement (A Medieval Mirror, 1984)
  - University of Iowa Center for the Book, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    Advertisement for Paper Samples
  - USC Fine Arts Press (Box 11, Folder 24)
    2 Publication Announcements (The Letter of Columbus, Coranto - Periodical)
  - W. Thomas Taylor, 1983-1989 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Keepsake for Book Club of Texas (Reprinted Review of My First Thirty Years), 2 Announcements of Availability for Sale (33 Autograph Letters of John Locke, Shakespeare Head Press The Works), 4 Publication Announcements (Twelve Bindings; Adrian Wilson, 1983; Reprints of Early French and English Binding-Marbling Manuals, 1987; Bruce Rogers, 1988)
  - Warwick Press (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Business Card, 2 Publication Announcements (On Becoming Three and Thirty; A Poultry Piece)
  - Waters Family, 1978-1989 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    Christmas Cards (1985, 1987, 1989), Prospectus for Calligraphy Prings with Miniature Proofs and Photo (1978)
  - Whittington Press, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Prospectus, Invitation
  - William Kaufman, Inc., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    Publication Announcement (The Hunting of the Snark, 1981)
  - Windell Press, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    Publication Announcement (Ines Reigned in Death, 1988)
  - Windhover Press (Box 11, Folder 31)